{
    "subject": "resource/Harold_Wilson",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Wilson, James Harold, Baron Wilson of Rievaulx",
    "human_readable": "The name of Harold Wilson is Wilson, James Harold, Baron Wilson of Rievaulx.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9882707595825195,
            "question": "Who is James Harold, Baron Wilson of Rievaulx?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8842337727546692,
            "question": "Which name is associated with Harold Wilson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8499224781990051,
            "question": "What was Harold Wilson's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8225411176681519,
            "question": "What was Harold Wilson known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8042687177658081,
            "question": "What did Harold Wilson become known as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7858557105064392,
            "question": "What title was Harold Wilson given?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7822472453117371,
            "question": "Is there more to Harold Wilson's name than 'Wilson'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7704766988754272,
            "question": "What is Harold Wilson's first name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6679660677909851,
            "question": "What title did Harold Wilson hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5225246548652649,
            "question": "How was Harold Wilson formally addressed?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Harold Wilson is Wilson, James Harold, Baron Wilson of Rievaulx.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2721_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What title did Harold Wilson hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2721_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Harold Wilson's first name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2721_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there more to Harold Wilson's name than 'Wilson'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2721_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2721_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2721_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2721_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2721_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2721_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2721_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2721_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2721_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2721_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2721_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents consistently refer to him as \"James Harold Wilson, Baron Wilson of Rievaulx\".  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that the full name of Harold Wilson is Wilson, James Harold, Baron Wilson of Rievaulx. The first document mentions his full name as \"James Harold Wilson (Baron Wilson of Rievaulx)\" and the subsequent documents also refer to him as \"James Harold Wilson, Baron Wilson of Rievaulx\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents contain the full name \"James Harold Wilson (Baron Wilson of Rievaulx),\" which confirms that his name is indeed Wilson, James Harold, Baron Wilson of Rievaulx."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}